<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>campaign &#8211; Mysql Rackspace</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/tag/campaign/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:07:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mysql.rackspace.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rackspace.png</url>
	<title>campaign &#8211; Mysql Rackspace</title>
	<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>cried the leader of the rescue team as he spoke of finding the wreckage of the Titan</title>
		<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/</link>
					<comments>https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[an accident]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[death]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Titanic ship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mysql.rackspace.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The head of the rescue team that found the wreckage of the tourist submarine Titan became emotional when talking about the operation. Ed Cassano, CEO of salvage group Pelagic Research Services, held a press conference last Friday. Cassano said at the press conference held at the company&#8217;s headquarters in New York, USA, that the members ... <a title="cried the leader of the rescue team as he spoke of finding the wreckage of the Titan" class="read-more" href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/" aria-label="More on cried the leader of the rescue team as he spoke of finding the wreckage of the Titan">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The head of the rescue team that found the wreckage of the tourist submarine Titan became emotional when talking about the operation.</p>



<p>Ed Cassano, CEO of salvage group Pelagic Research Services, held a press conference last Friday.</p>



<p>Cassano said at the press conference held at the company&#8217;s headquarters in New York, USA, that the members of his team who participated in this campaign became emotional.</p>



<p>On June 18, Titan lost contact with the wreckage on the bottom of the North Atlantic. Later, several countries including the United States started rescue operations.</p>



<p>On June 22, the US Coast Guard reported that some debris from the Titan had been found. Titan was destroyed by catastrophic inward pressure beneath the North Atlantic. All five occupants of the Titan were killed in the incident.</p>



<p>Cassano said his team was contacted only after Titan lost contact. Later, his company&#8217;s remote-controlled submarine Odysseus 6 reached the wreck of the Titanic.</p>



<p>The CEO of Pelagic Research Services said that shortly after Odysseus 6 arrived at the bottom of the ocean, they found the wreckage of Titan.</p>



<p>Cassano became emotional while speaking at the press conference. With tears in his voice, he requested everyone to accept the seriousness of the incident. At the same time, he asked to show respect to the emotions of the people who participated in this rescue operation.</p>



<p>Cassano said their rescue plan was to contain the Titan as soon as they found it. The scale of the rescue challenge was extreme.</p>



<p>The wreckage of the Titan was later brought ashore. The United States Coast Guard said the remains of the victims could be found in the wreckage.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
