<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>the mosquito &#8211; Mysql Rackspace</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/tag/the-mosquito/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:12:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mysql.rackspace.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rackspace.png</url>
	<title>the mosquito &#8211; Mysql Rackspace</title>
	<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Where mosquitoes are being killed by drones</title>
		<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/</link>
					<comments>https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the drone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the mosquito]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weird news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mysql.rackspace.com/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is difficult to find a person who has not suffered from mosquito bites. There are many ways to avoid mosquito bites. Some people use mosquito nets to avoid mosquito bites. Some use coils and even chemicals to kill mosquitoes. Therefore, the use of drones to kill mosquitoes will surely be the same as &#8216;cannons ... <a title="Where mosquitoes are being killed by drones" class="read-more" href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/" aria-label="More on Where mosquitoes are being killed by drones">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is difficult to find a person who has not suffered from mosquito bites. There are many ways to avoid mosquito bites. Some people use mosquito nets to avoid mosquito bites. Some use coils and even chemicals to kill mosquitoes. Therefore, the use of drones to kill mosquitoes will surely be the same as &#8216;cannons to kill mosquitoes&#8217;.</p>



<p>This happened. The authorities of Orange County, California, United States, have taken such a novel initiative to use drones after using many methods to kill mosquitoes without the expected results. Drones are seen spraying disinfectants in the lower areas, ponds and ponds to kill mosquitoes.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s winter in California. But it rains regularly. There is more mosquito breeding in it. The people of the whole area are fed up with the mosquitoes that are born in the stagnant water everywhere. Authorities have tried various ways to kill mosquitoes. They have decided to use drones as the latest method.</p>



<p>Irvine is home to the University of California. Near the town is a sanctuary called the Jan Joaquin Marsh Reserve. Disinfectants were recently sprayed there by drones. The drones were piloted by a man named John Savage. He said, &#8216;Because of the rain, there are a lot of mosquitoes here. Almost all reservoirs here are full of water. Because of this there are many mosquitoes.&#8217;</p>



<p>Orange County entomologist Kiet Nguyen said, &#8216;Mosquitoes have increased. We were looking for better technology to kill mosquitoes. A technology that can kill more and more mosquitoes faster. This is why drones are being used.&#8217;</p>



<p>Orange County authorities said they resorted to all conventional mosquito control methods. Special sprayers, trucks, helicopters—even airplanes—have used disinfectants. But it didn&#8217;t work. Therefore, they decided to use drones to kill mosquitoes, keeping in mind the fact that they can spray disinfectants in all areas, including those that are more specific. An acre area is being exterminated by a drone in just two minutes.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
