<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; Mysql Rackspace</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:12:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mysql.rackspace.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rackspace.png</url>
	<title>admin &#8211; Mysql Rackspace</title>
	<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Where mosquitoes are being killed by drones</title>
		<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/</link>
					<comments>https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the drone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the mosquito]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weird news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mysql.rackspace.com/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is difficult to find a person who has not suffered from mosquito bites. There are many ways to avoid mosquito bites. Some people use mosquito nets to avoid mosquito bites. Some use coils and even chemicals to kill mosquitoes. Therefore, the use of drones to kill mosquitoes will surely be the same as &#8216;cannons ... <a title="Where mosquitoes are being killed by drones" class="read-more" href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/" aria-label="More on Where mosquitoes are being killed by drones">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is difficult to find a person who has not suffered from mosquito bites. There are many ways to avoid mosquito bites. Some people use mosquito nets to avoid mosquito bites. Some use coils and even chemicals to kill mosquitoes. Therefore, the use of drones to kill mosquitoes will surely be the same as &#8216;cannons to kill mosquitoes&#8217;.</p>



<p>This happened. The authorities of Orange County, California, United States, have taken such a novel initiative to use drones after using many methods to kill mosquitoes without the expected results. Drones are seen spraying disinfectants in the lower areas, ponds and ponds to kill mosquitoes.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s winter in California. But it rains regularly. There is more mosquito breeding in it. The people of the whole area are fed up with the mosquitoes that are born in the stagnant water everywhere. Authorities have tried various ways to kill mosquitoes. They have decided to use drones as the latest method.</p>



<p>Irvine is home to the University of California. Near the town is a sanctuary called the Jan Joaquin Marsh Reserve. Disinfectants were recently sprayed there by drones. The drones were piloted by a man named John Savage. He said, &#8216;Because of the rain, there are a lot of mosquitoes here. Almost all reservoirs here are full of water. Because of this there are many mosquitoes.&#8217;</p>



<p>Orange County entomologist Kiet Nguyen said, &#8216;Mosquitoes have increased. We were looking for better technology to kill mosquitoes. A technology that can kill more and more mosquitoes faster. This is why drones are being used.&#8217;</p>



<p>Orange County authorities said they resorted to all conventional mosquito control methods. Special sprayers, trucks, helicopters—even airplanes—have used disinfectants. But it didn&#8217;t work. Therefore, they decided to use drones to kill mosquitoes, keeping in mind the fact that they can spray disinfectants in all areas, including those that are more specific. An acre area is being exterminated by a drone in just two minutes.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mysql.rackspace.com/where-mosquitoes-are-being-killed-by-drones/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>cried the leader of the rescue team as he spoke of finding the wreckage of the Titan</title>
		<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/</link>
					<comments>https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[an accident]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[campaign]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[death]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Titanic ship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mysql.rackspace.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The head of the rescue team that found the wreckage of the tourist submarine Titan became emotional when talking about the operation. Ed Cassano, CEO of salvage group Pelagic Research Services, held a press conference last Friday. Cassano said at the press conference held at the company&#8217;s headquarters in New York, USA, that the members ... <a title="cried the leader of the rescue team as he spoke of finding the wreckage of the Titan" class="read-more" href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/" aria-label="More on cried the leader of the rescue team as he spoke of finding the wreckage of the Titan">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The head of the rescue team that found the wreckage of the tourist submarine Titan became emotional when talking about the operation.</p>



<p>Ed Cassano, CEO of salvage group Pelagic Research Services, held a press conference last Friday.</p>



<p>Cassano said at the press conference held at the company&#8217;s headquarters in New York, USA, that the members of his team who participated in this campaign became emotional.</p>



<p>On June 18, Titan lost contact with the wreckage on the bottom of the North Atlantic. Later, several countries including the United States started rescue operations.</p>



<p>On June 22, the US Coast Guard reported that some debris from the Titan had been found. Titan was destroyed by catastrophic inward pressure beneath the North Atlantic. All five occupants of the Titan were killed in the incident.</p>



<p>Cassano said his team was contacted only after Titan lost contact. Later, his company&#8217;s remote-controlled submarine Odysseus 6 reached the wreck of the Titanic.</p>



<p>The CEO of Pelagic Research Services said that shortly after Odysseus 6 arrived at the bottom of the ocean, they found the wreckage of Titan.</p>



<p>Cassano became emotional while speaking at the press conference. With tears in his voice, he requested everyone to accept the seriousness of the incident. At the same time, he asked to show respect to the emotions of the people who participated in this rescue operation.</p>



<p>Cassano said their rescue plan was to contain the Titan as soon as they found it. The scale of the rescue challenge was extreme.</p>



<p>The wreckage of the Titan was later brought ashore. The United States Coast Guard said the remains of the victims could be found in the wreckage.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mysql.rackspace.com/cried-the-leader-of-the-rescue-team-as-he-spoke-of-finding-the-wreckage-of-the-titan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mother blames only one person for killing Nahel</title>
		<link>https://mysql.rackspace.com/mother-blames-only-one-person-for-killing-nahel/</link>
					<comments>https://mysql.rackspace.com/mother-blames-only-one-person-for-killing-nahel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[France]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[killed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[murder]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[protest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shot]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the police]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mysql.rackspace.com/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Algerian-born Monia, the mother of teenager Nahel Em, who was shot dead by police in France, said she considered her son a &#8216;best friend&#8217;. The boy was his life. After the death of her son, the mother became rebellious. But he did not blame the entire police force as many did. &#8220;I blame only one ... <a title="Mother blames only one person for killing Nahel" class="read-more" href="https://mysql.rackspace.com/mother-blames-only-one-person-for-killing-nahel/" aria-label="More on Mother blames only one person for killing Nahel">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Algerian-born Monia, the mother of teenager Nahel Em, who was shot dead by police in France, said she considered her son a &#8216;best friend&#8217;. The boy was his life.</p>



<p>After the death of her son, the mother became rebellious. But he did not blame the entire police force as many did. &#8220;I blame only one person who took my son&#8217;s life,&#8221; he said.</p>



<p>As the mother is of Algerian origin, Nahel&#8217;s death has worried the Algerian government across the Mediterranean. However, it is not yet officially known whether Nahel was a dual citizen or not.</p>



<p>The Algerian Ministry of Foreign Affairs expressed the opinion that Nahel&#8217;s death was a &#8216;terror&#8217; in an event. They called Nahel an Algerian, saying his protection was in the hands of France.</p>



<p>Nahel was shot dead by the police at a checkpoint while driving on Tuesday. Protests are ongoing across the country against this killing. This protest took place on the fifth day today. Yesterday, Saturday night, 719 protesters were arrested. And the previous night about 1000 people were arrested. 45 thousand police have been deployed in the country to quell the protests.</p>



<p>17-year-old Nahel grew up in an estate named after Pablo Picasso in the city of Notre-Dame, west of Paris. This estate is residential. The mother brought up Nahel, the only child. He used to work as a delivery man. His father is not known.</p>



<p>For the past three years, Nahel has played for the Pirates of Nate rugby club. An association called Ovale Citienne runs a program for teenagers who are having trouble adjusting to school. Nahel also participated in that program.</p>



<p>Police have no criminal record against Nahel. Nate&#8217;s counsel said that when the checkpoint police asked him to stop, he did not. He was summoned to appear in an upcoming juvenile court appearance.</p>



<p>Police said last Tuesday that he had attracted their attention due to reckless driving.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mysql.rackspace.com/mother-blames-only-one-person-for-killing-nahel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
